flyaji.com 2014-11-18

# Privacy Policy

AJI has no intention of and will not be involved in or party to transactions that require exploiting, exchanging, leasing and/or sharing your private information, especially your email addresses, phone numbers, and contact details without your direct permission and approval, with any party that we are affiliated with unless and until required by the law we abide by and conform to. Should we opt to alter some or all of the clauses of our privacy policy we will update the changes here. We may also choose to email our registered users with the new details. If required by law, we will we obtain your consent to make these alterations.

We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 12. If you are under the age of 12, please do not provide your contact information of any kind whatsoever. If you are a Parent or Guardian of someone under the age of 12 who has provided us information without your knowledge and consent, please contact us. Upon sharing personal information for the purchase of a ticket, the user is entitled to be accountable to concur to all the mandatory costs, fees, taxes and agreements that arise from use of this website purchase of our services.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy;

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Cookie Policy**

A 'cookie' is a part of text stored on your computer, workstation, phone or any device used to surf the Internet. Cookies fundamentally, are used to store personal information about you on your computer, or to help provide a service that you request. AJI uses cookies to ensure the best possible experience on our website. If you continue to browse our website without changing your settings you agree to receive cookies from AJI. However, if you prefer, you can change your cookie settings at any time. AJI handles and protects information that the company possesses under the following: 

  * We routinely undertake safety measures to disallow inappropriate access to information including leakage, elimination and fabrication.
  * In the case of an accident, we work towards minimizing damage through quickly and helpful release of necessary information. We will take all precautionary steps to prevent a reoccurrence.
  * We comply with internal and international policies, regulations and guidelines.
  * We have implemented awareness programs for employees that ensure that customer data is suitably managed, while striving to improve knowledge and customer experience.
  * Our contracts with external parties and vendors mandate discretion and guarantees that the information will be adequately managed.
